Nkenge Touré Papers, circa 1968-2014
Sophia Smith Collection
- SERIES VII. AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS
  - Audiocassettes (Box 9)
    - [Unknown], "Farm Coop, Banana Plant," 27 Sep ? (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - [Unknown], "Bluefields History/Orientation," undated (Box 10, Folder 23)
- SERIES VIII. OVERSIZE MATERIALS
  - Washington Afro American newspaper, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Washington Peace Center Newsletter, Dec. 1980 [see Yulanda Ward Memorial, Series IV, Box 7] (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - "Why was Yulanda Ward Assassinated?" poster (Box 11, Folder 3)
    [see Yulanda Ward Memorial, Series IV, Box 7]
  - Upfront newspaper, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    [see D.C. Rape Crisis Center, Series IV, Box 4-5]
  - Nommo newspaper, 1991. (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - The New Black Panther newsletter, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    [See series IV, Box 4]
  - March for Women's Lives posters, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    [See series IV, Box 5]